A Guide to the Rockefeller Family Fund records FA1271
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family Fund records
1968-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family Fund
FA1271
217.46 Cubic Feet 166 record storage boxes and 37 bound volumes.
Conditions Governing Access
Annual reports are open for research. All other paper records are restricted.
Arrangement
Arranged in series by file type.
Series 1: Annual Reports.
Scope and Contents
Open collection contains annual reports only.
- Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Reports, 1968-2005; 1; 37 Bound Volumes 37 bound volumes
  Arrangement
  Chronological
  Annual reports
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1968-1969 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1968-69)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1970-1971 (Item REF 3606 ROC 1970-71)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1972 (REF 360.62 ROC 1972)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1973 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1973)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1974 (Item REF 360.6 ROC 1974)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1975 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1975)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1976 (Item REF 30.62 ROC 1976)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1977 (Item REF 360.6 ROC 1977)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1978 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1978)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1979 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1979)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1980 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1980)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1981 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1981)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1982 (Item RF 360.2 ROC 1982)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1983 (Item REF 360.6 ROC 1983)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1984 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1984)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1985 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1985)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1986 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1986)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1987 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1987)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1988 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1988)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1989 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1989)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1990 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1990)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1991 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1991)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1992 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1992)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1993 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1993)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1994 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1994)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1995 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1995)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1996 (Item REF 360.6 ROC 1996)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1997 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1997)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1998 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 1998)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 1999 (Item REF 60.62 ROC 1999)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2000 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2000)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2001 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2001)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2002 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2002)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2003 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2003)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2004 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2004)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund Annual Report 2005 (Item REF 360.62 ROC 2005)
- Grants, 1985-2004, 2
  - AAUW Legal Advocacy Fund, Inc. (Box G1)
  - Action Against Crime and Violence Education Fund (Box G1)
  - The Adirondack Council, Inc. (Box G1)
  - Alaska Center for the Environment (Box G1)
  - Alaska Conservation Alliance (Box G1)
  - Alaska Conservation Voters (Box G1)
  - Alaskan Forum for Environmental Responsibility (Box G1)
  - Alaskan Conservation Foundation, I (Box G1)
  - Alaska Conservation Foundation, II (Box G1)
  - Alliance for Affordable Energy (Box G1)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (Box G1)
  - Alliance for Justice (Box G1)
  - Alliance for Nuclear Accountability (Box G1)
  - Alliance to End Childhood Lead Poisoning (Box G2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Inc., Center for National Security Studies (Box G2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Inc., Women's Rights Project (Box G2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Inc., Virginia (Box G2)
  - American Community Protection Association (Box G2)
  - American Environment, Inc. (Box G2)
  - American Institute for Social Justice (Box G2)
  - American Lands Alliance (Box G2)
  - American Lands Campaign (Box G2)
  - American Ocean Campaign (Box G2)
  - American Rivers Inc. (Box G2)
  - Americans for Civic Participation (Box G2)
  - A. Philip Randolph Educational Fund (Box G2)
  - Appalachian Center for the Economy and the Environment (Box G2)
  - Association for the Children Education of Support, Inc. (Box G3)
  - Association for Union Democracy, Inc. (Box G3)
  - Association of Forest Service Employees for Environmental Ethics (AFSEEE) Inc. (Box G3)
  - Association of New Jersey Environmental Commissions (Box G3)
  - Atlanta Community Food Banks, Inc. (Box G3)
  - Audubon Society of New Hampshire (Box G3)
  - Austin Interfaith Sponsoring Committee (Texas Interfaith Education Fund) (Box G3)
  - Ballot Initiative Strategy Center Foundation (Box G3)
  - Benton Foundation (Box G3)
  - Bluewater Network (Box G3)
  - Boston Women's Health Book Collective, Inc. (Box G3)
  - Bread and Roses Cultural Project, Inc. (Box G3)
  - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. (Box G3)
  - California Leagues of Conservation Voters (Box G3)
  - California Toxics Actions dba CBE (Box G3)
  - California Voter Foundation (Box G3)
  - Campaign Finance Research Institute (Box G4)
  - Campaign for a Prospective Georgia (Box G4)
  - Carolina Community Project, Inc. (Box G4)
  - The Center for Auto Safety (Box G4)
  - Center for Biological Diverity (Box G4)
  - Center for Community Change (Funder's Committee for Voter Registration & Education) (Box G4)
  - Center for Community Change (Neighborhood Revitalization Project) (Box G4)
  - Center for Community Change (Women's Technical Assistance Project} (Box G4)
  - Center for Government Studies, Inc. (Box G4)
  - Center for Health, Environment and Justice I (Box G4)
  - Center for Health, Environment and Justice II (Box G4)
  - Center for Health, Environment and Justice (Health Care Without Harm) (Box G4)
  - Center for Investigative Reporting, Inc. (Box G4)
  - Center for Law and Social Policy (Box G4)
  - Center for Marine Conservation (Box G5)
  - Center for a New American Dream (Box G5)
  - Center for Non-Profit Corporations, Inc. (Box G5)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives - I (Box G5)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives - II (Box G5)
  - Center for Population Options (Box G5)
  - Center for Psychological Studies in the Nuclear Age (Box G5)
  - Center for Public Integrity (Box G5)
  - Center for Public Interest Research (Box G5)
  - Center for Responsive Politics (Box G5)
  - Center for the Study of Public Policy, Inc. (Box G5)
  - Center for Women's Policy Studies (Box G5)
  - Center for Women's Economic Alternatives, Inc. (Box G6)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - I (Box G6)
  - Center for Budget and Policy Priorities - II (Box G6)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation (Box G6)
  - Chicago Women in Trades (Box G6)
  - Child Care Law Center (Box G6)
  - Children's Defense Fund (Box G6)
  - Citizen's Alert (Box G6)
  - Citizens Coal Council (Box G6)
  - Citizens for a Better Environment, Chicago (Box G6)
  - Citizens Legal Clinic (Box G6)
  - Citizens Participation Project (Box G6)
  - Citizens Vote, Inc. (Box G6)
  - CLCV Education Fund (Box G7)
  - Clean Airport Partnership, Inc. (Box G7)
  - Clean Indoor Ari Educational Foundation (Box G7)
  - Clear Water Action (Box G7)
  - Clean Water Fund (Box G7)
  - Coal Employment Project (Box G7)
  - Coalition to Restore Coastal Louisiana (Box G7)
  - Coast Alliance (Box G7)
  - Colorado Environmental Coalition (Box G7)
  - Colorado Women's Agenda (Box G7)
  - Commission on Religion on Appalachia, Inc. (Box G7)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. (Box G7)
  - Communications Consortium Media Center (Box G7)
  - Community Catalyst, Inc. (Box G7)
  - Community Shares of Colorado, Inc. (Box G7)
  - Community Shares of Wisconsin, Inc. (Box G7)
  - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility (Box G8)
- Administrative records, 3
- Financial and Accounting records, 4